MightyCall Mobile

Solutions

* Solutions
* By industry

Product

Resources

Support

Menu

  [ ](https://www.mightycall.com/)Menu

Solutions

* Solutions
* By industry

[Pricing

 ](https://www.mightycall.com/pricing/) 

Product

Resources

Support

Close

Submit a Ticket

Thanks for your request! We'll get back to you shortly

Please fill in the field

Please fill in the field

Enter a correct email address

You can attach one supporting file with a 10 Mb size limit in .png, .jpg, or .pdf format

File size limit 10 Mb (.png,.jpg,.jpeg,.pdf)

File size more than 10 Mb

Privacy Policy
==============

**MIGHTYCALL**  
**PRIVACY POLICY**  
**EFFECTIVE DATE: July 1, 2023**

This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way CallCurrent, Inc., a Delaware corporation (Trademark MightyCall) (together with its affiliates: “MightyCall”, “we” or “us”) MightyCall regarding your use of MightyCall’s call management solutions and other services and any software (“Software”) provided for your use in connection with our solutions or services (such solutions, services and Software, collectively, the “Service”).

MightyCall uses a single Privacy Policy that addresses our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) when you use our Service, including through your mobile device, browser and/or extensions, or your desk phone.

This Policy applies to all Customers and Users. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information.

As used in this Policy, the terms listed below have the following meanings:

* Customer – A “Customer” is anyone who uses MightyCall services. When a Customer subscribing, purchasing services for use by others, those individuals also may be considered Customers for purposes of this Policy.
* User – A “User” is anyone who visits our websites.
*  Personal Information – “Personal Information” is information that directly identifies or reasonably can be used to identify an individual Customer or User. Examples include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, ID, credit card number (Visa, MasterCard, or American Express) and/or Apple pay, and/or PayPal account.
* Website – “Website” means any page or location on the Internet, no matter what device (cell phone, lap top, PC, etc.) or protocol (http, WAP, ftp or other) is used to access the page or location. In this Policy, we use the term website other similar terms such as “Internet site,” “site,” and “web page.”

What We Collect
---------------

We collect a variety of Personal information about Customers and Users in order to ensure an enjoyable user experience and seamless communications.

When you create a MightyCall account, you provide us with Personal Information such as your name, email address, phone number, password, and payment method, such as a valid credit card (including proper billing information) or Apple pay  or PayPal account.

If you provide your third-party account credentials to us or sign in to the Services through a third party site or service, such as Google, some information from those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions. That Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. Additionally, Dialpad’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google Accounts will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy), including the Limited Use requirements.

You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features within the Services.

When you interact with the Service, we automatically receive and record information that we then use to provide the Service.

Device and Session Information: We collect information about your browser or device, which may include your IP address, device IDs, or other unique identifiers, cookie information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Service, and the page or feature you requested. We use this data to customize your experience with our Service, based on your usage patterns. We also use it to improve the Service – for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Service, and we can use that knowledge to make decisions about future development focus. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features.

Telephony Information: We maintain customer call records such as time, duration, the number of the called party. Like all telephony services, we also maintain temporary copies of call audio for up to 24 hours for quality assurance.

Integrations: MightyCall offers the option to integrate the Service with products or services of third parties, such as Google, Salesforce, Zendesk, HubSpot, and others. If you enable those integrations, including providing credential information to MightyCall and/or the third party, any data that MightyCall collects from or shares to these integrations partners are subject to this Privacy Policy.

How We Use Personal Information
-------------------------------

In general, MightyCall uses personal information to serve our existing and prospective customers and to enhance and extend our customer relationships. MightyCall uses Personal Information to deliver the Services, and also to improve the Services and to communicate with you about the Services, including marketing communications.

The main ways that we use the Personal Information that you provide to us or that we collect when you use the Service are to:

* deliver the Service, including placing and receiving voice calls, providing call recordings, voicemails, and transcriptions; determining your geographic location for efficient call routing;  organizing your contacts lists; uploading  your contacts lists and/or media files (images, photos, etc.);
* manage your billing, to provide services or complete transactions you have requested;
* prevent, detect, and investigate potentially prohibited or illegal activities, including fraud and violations of our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy.

MightyCall may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you promotional email offers, or email you about your use of the Service, or inform you about MightyCall services we think will interest you.

Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more applicable and improve our services. If you do not want to receive communications from us, you can always opt out by unsubscribing through the link at the bottom of our emails or by contacting us [support@mightycall.com](mailto:support@mightycall.com).

By providing your phone number, you agree to receive SMS messages from MightyCall. Message & data rates may apply; message frequency may vary. You can reply STOP to unsubscribe anytime.

Despite you may choose not to receive marketing information from us, you will continue to receive invoices, customer service-related notifications and other information, related to each service you purchase or subscribe to, from us electronically or otherwise.

MightyCall uses Personal Information to improve or validate its features, and may securely share it with contractors to do so on MightyCall’s behalf. You can control what data is stored by choosing which MightyCall features you use from the settings menu in the relevant Service.

We do not use Personal Information to make automated decisions.

Periodically, you may be able to participate in our surveys to help us improve our services. Any personal information collected from you in a survey will ONLY be used internally by MightyCall and in accordance with this Policy.

Disclosure of Personal Information
----------------------------------

We do not sell your personal information to anyone for any purpose, and we maintain information about you in our business records while you are a customer, or until it is no longer needed for business, tax, or legal purposes.

MightyCall may disclose your personal information if you consent to the disclosure in advance. Depending on the service, we may obtain your consent in writing or verbally.

MightyCall reserves the right to release personal information without your consent when we believe release is appropriate to do one of the following:

* Comply with the law (e.g., lawful subpoena or court order);
* Enforce or apply our agreements to sell or provide services to you;
* Bill and collect for services; or
* Protect out rights or property (e.g., to address allegations about fraudulent or unlawful activity on an MightyCall account).

We may share your personal data between our business affiliates where it is necessary to perform the services provided to you.

In order to verify payment methods and prevent fraud, MightyCall verifies personal information, including payment information, with payment providers and fraud prevention services. If at any time you apply for a credit with us, we may perform a credit inquiry with credit reporting agencies, and such inquiry may be noted on your credit record. We may use automated decision making systems to verify payment methods, assess creditworthiness, or prevent fraud, and we may contact you requesting additional information when needed.

We may share your personal information with Third Parties only as necessary to complete a transaction or perform a service that you have requested, or to support the technical operation and maintenance of our services and of our website. We require those Third Parties to protect any personal information they may receive in a manner consistent with this Policy.

We do not provide personal information to Third Parties for the marketing of their own products and services without your consent.

Information that’s no longer personally identifiable
----------------------------------------------------

We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identifiable, and provide that information to certain of our partners to help us improve our Service, such as sending anonymized samples of audio or text messages (SMS/MMS) to a third party to improve speech-to-text transcription and reading comprehension. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services. However, we never disclose aggregate usage information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual.

Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)
-----------------------------------------------

MightyCall collects and maintains certain customer proprietary network information (“CPNI”) while providing telecommunications and interconnected voice-over-Internet-protocol (“interconnected VoIP”) services to its users and customers. Your CPNI includes the types of telecommunications and interconnected VoIP services you currently purchase or subscribe to, how you use those services (for example, your calling records), and billing information related to those services. Your MightyCall telephone number, name and address do not constitute CPNI.

MightyCall does not sell, trade or otherwise share your CPNI with anyone outside of MightyCall or with anyone who is not authorized to represent us to offer our services or to perform functions on our behalf, except as the law may require or you may authorize.

We may use or disclose your CPNI for legal or regulatory reasons such as to respond to a court order, to investigate fraud, to protect our rights or property, to protect against the unlawful use of our services, or to protect other users. You have a right and we have a duty under federal law to protect the confidentiality of your CPNI.

Use of Cookies
--------------

MightyCall uses “cookies” to enhance your use of our website. “Cookies” are small text files placed on your computer’s hard drive by a website when you visit that website. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit to a website so that when you return to that site, the site operator knows who you are and can personalize your visit. For example, cookies enable a website shopping cart to function so that you only have to check out once. Consequently, cookies are often tied to the use of personally identifiable information while using our website. If you choose not to accept the use of cookies, your use of our website may be impaired.

Cookies allow us to do the following:

* Complete transactions you have requested;
* Collect information to determine which services and sections of our website are most and least popular;
* Personalize our website and make recommendations to you based on services you have used in the past; and
* Improve the ease of use of our website, sometimes in conjunction with web beacons.

MightyCall does not use cookies to store credit card information. MightyCall does, however, use cookies to store login information for customers who choose the option of storing such information on their computers.

MightyCall also uses a session-based cookie to maintain continuity of navigation for you when viewing our website during a particular on-line session. After closing the browser, the session cookie simply terminates; it is not stored on your computer’s hard drive thereafter.

MightyCall gathers this data using cookies (both first party cookies, such as the Google Analytics cookie, and third-party cookies, such as the DoubleClick cookie), web beacons, tags, and other similar techniques that deliver small files to your computer and which allow these networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers.

MightyCall uses certain third-party services that help us understand traffic on our website in various ways: Google Analytics and Google Adwords help MightyCall understand who is visiting MightyCall’s websites and to show relevant ads on other websites to people who have visited MightyCall’s websites. You can control what ads you see through the [Google Ad Settings Manager](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).

User Profiles and Contacts
--------------------------

Certain user profile information, including your profile photo and status, may be displayed to other users within the Services. You are responsible for entering and updating that content. Additionally, if you sign into the Services through a third party service, your list of contacts from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Services.

How is my personal information secured?
---------------------------------------

Your account is protected by a password, and your Personal Information is encrypted in transit and in storage using industry standard encryption. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service.

You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security.

How can I access, manage and delete my data?
--------------------------------------------

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit, or delete the following information you’ve provided to us:

* name and password
* email address
* phone number(s)
* location
* time zone
* recorded/transcribed messages and calls, and voicemails
* call history including incoming/outgoing number and duration
* user profile information, including images you have uploaded
* billing information
* contacts
* other third-party account information you have linked to the site.

Following the cancellation of your Services, MightyCall will delete and/or anonymize information related to your account so that no personal information is retained by MightyCall or its contractors, unless otherwise required by law.

Compliance with specific state and country laws
-----------------------------------------------

**Europe and GDPR**

Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you are the controller of your personal data and MightyCall is a data Processor. As Processor, MightyCall will comply with the instructions contained in this document, in the MightyCall Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy, and in any agreements between you and MightyCall, or other instructions that you provide later.

Subject to EU law, you have the following rights in relation to your Personal Data:

Right of access: If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and, if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data along with certain other details. If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee.

Right to rectification: If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask that we correct or complete it.

Right to erasure: You may ask us to erase your Personal Data in some circumstances, such as where we no longer need it or you withdraw your consent (where applicable).

Right to restrict processing: You may ask us to restrict or ‘block’ the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as where you contest the accuracy of the data or object to us processing it (please read below for information on your right to object).

Right to data portability: You have the right to obtain your Personal Data from us that you consented to give us or that was provided to us as necessary in connection with our contract with you where we process that Personal Data in an automated way. We will give you your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.

Right to object: You may ask us at any time to stop processing your Personal Data, and we will do so if we are relying on a legitimate interest to process your Personal Data — unless we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing; or if we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing.

Rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling: You have the right to be free from decisions based solely on automated processing of your Personal Data, including profiling, unless this is necessary in relation to a contract between you and us or you provide your explicit consent to this use. MightyCall does not perform automated decision-making.

Right to withdraw consent: If we rely on your consent to process your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, but this will not affect any processing of your data that has already taken place.

We will keep your Personal Data for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, while we have a legitimate business need to do so in connection with your account, or as required by law (e.g. for tax, legal, accounting or other purposes), whichever is longer.

**California and CCPA**

MightyCall complies with the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) and related laws. Details on the rights and disclosures relevant to California residents are available in the CCPA Addendum to MightyCall’s privacy policy.

**OPPA Compliance Statement**

MightyCall does not provide services designed for use by children under the age of 13, nor does it knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected such information we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 has provided us personal information, please contact us at [support@mightycall.com](mailto:support@mightycall.com).

Contacting Us
-------------

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, you may contact us at:

**CallCurrent, Inc.**  
919 North Market Street  
Suite 950  
Wilmington, DE, 19801

email: [support@mightycall.com](mailto:support@mightycall.com)

919 North Market Street, Suite 950 Wilmington, DE, 19801

Company

Support

Resources

Features

Solutions

Phone Numbers

Toll-free Area Codes

Toll-Free Numbers

VoIP Features

VoIP Solutions
